I've finally arrived!
Time to find Tachibanakan.
Episode 1: New Life!
My name is Natsuno Hanabi.
I'm 15, and this spring, I'm finally going to be a high school student.
I've moved here from Tokyo,
Tachibanakan
and as of today, I'll be living at
Tachibanakan, a high school dorm.
Tachibanakan
Hype!
Is this...
Tachibanakan?!
Did I get the wrong address?
The moment I saw her, it felt like her beauty was drawing me in.
She had silky silver hair, and skin as white as snow.
I could see light pink cherries atop her skin...
Wait, cherries?!
Um...
Don't just stand out here. Come on in.
The door's open.
She's got cherries, too.
Huh? Why's a kid here?
You're short too, you know!
S-So what?! I'm going into high school this year!
Hang on. Did you forget?
Huh?
Hey!
Hold on a second! I want to ask you—
Oh my, you must be Natsuno Hanabi.
Welcome to Tachibanakan!
Tachibana
kaaan
Huh?
Tachibana
kaaan
Um...
Tachibanakan
Did you just say that this was Tachibanakan?
Huh?
Tachibanakan
The one and only!
I-It's nothing like what I imagined.
This can't be...
Oh, no! Turn that frown upside down!
It's okay.
Your big sister will make you feel better.
Y-Yoriko?
Oh, I forgot to introduce myself.
My name is Fujiwara Yoriko.
I'm the manager here.
Huh? Why does "Yoriko" sound so...
Yori! Quit smothering Hanabi!
Aw...
You know my name?
Hmph!
Hanabi!
We're the Natsuno family.
We just moved in next door.
We're the Fujiwaras.
Aren't you a cute one!
You look about the same age as Konomi.
Oh, I see.
She still remembers me.
How could I forget?
The beautiful scenery and clear water almost made me forget the six years it had been
since I left the town where I grew up.
It couldn't have been a better day to mark the start of my new life.
At least, that should have been the case,
but Yoriko wanted to hear about everything from back then.
You're Hanabi?! The same one that moved away six years ago?!
I couldn't tell!
Oh, yeah...
Who was that girl, anyway?
Why was she naked?
Hey there, new girl.
So, whaddya think of Yoriko's boobs?
Sh-Sh...
She's not wearing anything down there.