looks like it hurt...
I guess greeting someone without panties would surprise anybody!
It's okay.
Sorry about that.
My name is Tsukishiro Yuu.
Call me Yuu.
I'm Natsuno Hanabi.
Nice to meet y—
Episode 2: Secret Place
Stop it...
C'mon, we're just bonding!
That's not the problem!
Rumble
Hey!
EXPLOSION
Cut it out, Yuu!
Quit perving out on our guest!
Kono, Hana's a resident here at Tachibanakan now.
No, she's still a guest to me!
Are you jealous?
Jealous types end up alone, you know?
That's not the problem.
I hope the two of you throw up in your sleep and choke on the vomit and die!
The day you left for Tokyo,
Kono wouldn't stop crying.
She must have really loved you.
I'm sure she's happy to see you,
but she has a lot of difficult emotions to work through.
She might be worried that you forgot her,
or that you're not happy to see her.
Have you told her how you feel yet?
I think this was the place.
I found you.
You remembered.
We would catch freshwater crabs, play house,
and find all sorts of pretty rocks.
This was our...
...secret place.
But you forgot about me, didn't you?
Well, you look so much more grown up, and a lot cuter.
I couldn't tell at first.
It's been six years, after all.
I'm happy.
Let's play together a whole lot more, Konomi.
It's a little weird hearing that again after so long,
Hanabi.
How about we head back?
Yeah.
You should hop in the bath and warm up before you catch a cold.
Yup.
Oh, I know.
I think Kono's out of the bath,
so you should take one next, Hana.
I want in, too!
Open up!
If you don't open up, I'll ***** you with a ***** and ***** you all day!
Ahh!
Whaa!
I can't hold her back...
Bam!!
Slip
Splash!!
What are you doing?!
Bang!!
Peep, peep.
Stick
M-My eye!
I can't get it out...
Crash
Hanabi, I'm sorry about yesterday.
I went kinda overboard, too.
Breakfast's ready.
No!
I'm Takamura Iori. Nice to meet you.
Just what is my life here going to be like?!
PLEASE
LISTEN
TO
THE
WORDS
PLEASE
LISTEN
TO
THE
WORDS
PLEASE
LISTEN
TO
THE
WORDS
The ABC's of love are just a delusion,
so forge the forbidden covenant with me instead
A legacy we shan't ever constrain
Bow down to holy judgment
Dressed as you were born into this world
Now, it's time to draw the curtains
And our cries will resonate
So give me more and more and more and more!