So what's the plan now?
Let me see...
First, we need to get these
people somewhere safe.
Easier said than done.
Battlefields aren't exactly teeming with safe havens.
Then can you take us to Maruruha?
Most of them come from there.
Maruruha is a capital city near the border.
It was captured by the Uzuurussha
at the start of the battle.
I expect it's under their control now.
So we're jumping right into enemy territory?
But that means Oshutoru and the
others are heading there now, right?
That's mighty fine then!
We can just have a little reunion of sorts!
Agreed.
Then let's get moving.
Sorry.
Just hang in there a bit longer.
I'm just fine!
I'm my daddy's little girl, after all.
That's very reassuring!
Don't get too attached, or it's going to be hard to say goodbye later.
Then why don't we simply
have them stay with us?
Yakutowaruto-san seems pretty
handy to have around.
Give me a break.
Looks about what, six thousand?
Three thousand for me,
and three thousand for you.
Hardly a problem.
Forward!
The     False     Mask
Episode 15
Masks
Reporting, sir.
Mikazuchi-sama and Oshutoru-sama have
succeeded in rescuing Dekoponpo-sama.
Naturally.
Mikazuchi is my brother, after all.
Yes.
As per your original plan,
the arrival of all the Pillar Generals, including the Royal Generals,
has drastically altered the flow of the battle.
Munechika-sama, the Guardian Protector,
has intercepted the enemy at the riverbanks.
Vurai-sama of the Mighty Arm has initiated
large-scale combat in the canyons.
Your forces, Raikou-sama,
have deployed in the forests.
Finally, Oshutoru-sama and Mikazuchi-sama
have headed towards the Uzuurussha's main camp in Maruruha, acting independently.
War is not merely a contest of numbers.
No matter how many thousands they bring,
they are no match for the Eight Pillar Generals.
Indeed.
All preparations are complete.
The Emperor has given his orders.
Now they will learn what it means
to turn their blades against Yamato.
So the Yamato dogs have hidden in the forest to confuse us?
Damned cowards.
Fools. We Uzuurussha are nomads.
We know well how to fight in the forest.
What?
Archers?
Calm down! They can't see into the forest!
Their arrows won't hit us!
But—
Impossible!
How do they know exactly where we are?
Archers are to continue firing and
push the rats back to 4-2-3-4.
Infantry, move to 4-5-4-1.
What?
Checkmate.
Dance in the palm of my hand
to this melody I play for you.
You shall intrude upon this land no further.
You shall not pass!
This territory is now under my possession.
If you value your lives, retreat.
What are you doing!?
Charge forth!
Crush her!
Very well.
To protect the people,
I shall become a man-eating demon
and destroy all who oppose me.
Impossible... Impossible!
A battle this one-sided isn't possible!
The Emperor has ordered your deaths!
Get going!
Or you know what'll happen to your families!
Go!
Move!
Good luck!
Dance! Dance!
I have no end of pawns to sacrifice!
That's one of the Eight Pillar Generals!
S-Save us!
They took my wife and child...
Please, save us!
We had no choice but this!
Please show mercy!
The Emperor has ordered me
to destroy all in my path.
What happened?
What's going on?
That can't be—
F-Full retreat!
Run!
Ouro, all our forces deployed into
Yamato's territory have been wiped out.
The enemy is almost upon us.
We're holding them off for the moment,
but it's only a matter of time
until they break through.
Your decision, my lord.
My decision?
Yes.
We should move west.
As long as you're alive, we can rebuild.
Now is the time to endure.
So you're telling me to retreat?
To abandon this land?
Ouro, I humbly beg you.
Very well.
We shall move west.
Ouro...
But this is not a retreat!
It's a change of direction!
Yes, sir!
Father...
So they're abandoning the
fortress and retreating?
Weaklings.
We'll follow them, Mikazuchi.
Of course.
Then let us see who can bring
back the enemy general's head.
You're on.
Entua, are you still alive?
If you still have your life, don't throw it away.
Even if it means drinking from muddy waters.
Once we're past this valley,
it won't be easy for them to follow us.
We'll hide in the darkness and
get as far to the west as we can.
Z-Zeguni-sama!
Stay calm.
You men protect the Ouro and cross the bridge quickly.
But...
Go!
What are you trying to achieve?
I will not allow you to cross.
You shall not pass!
No, you will.
The Emperor has ordered your deaths.
I see.
If that's the case, then...
Did I not say that you would not cross?
I said YOU SHALL NOT PASS, balrog scum!
This man...
He would sacrifice his life to protect his lord?
You may have him.
I'll go around the valley and
pursue the barbarian chieftain.
Understood.
Father!
So the Uzuurussha's main force
has retreated already?
Yes.
Big Brother and Mikazuchi-sama
have followed in pursuit.
But there are still many
soldiers in the fortress.
Just surrender already!
I shall personally guarantee your safety!
W-Watch it!
Hey! I'm trying to be nice here!
I don't think you're in the position for that.
Sister, I believe an appeal to their emotions would be the best option here.
Hey, come on, misters!
Your mas are cryin' back home!
A-Are you hungry?
If you'd like, I'll bring you something...
There are injured in there, right?
So could you come out?
I want to treat them.
I truly appreciate everything you've done.
It's fine.
Is this goodbye, then?
I doubt we'll ever meet again, but stay well.
Oh, about that.
I'm leaving them here, but...
Shinonon and I were thinking of
sticking with you a while longer.
Seriously?
I'm not from Maruruha to begin with.
And Kuon made us an offer.
Above all, I owe you for saving me.
So it looks like you'll be seeing us around.
I still have no say in this stuff, huh?
Well, two more won't make that
much of a difference at this point.
What's that?
This is...
Shinonon!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thank you, Kokopo!
Much obliged!
You saved us!
Thank you.
You have my gratitude.
Shinonon!
Daddy!
The capital, Maruruha, is right past that!
Reporting!
Multiple enemy units have concealed
themselves within Maruruha!
What is that?
Vurai...
One of the Eight Pillar Generals...
Vurai of the Mighty Arm.
That's...
An Akuruturuka.
Akuruturuka?
Only warriors chosen by
the Emperor and the masks
can unleash their power to assume that form.
Masks...
You mean Oshutoru can too?
Yes.
H-Help me!
Hey, that's dangerous!
My family's there!
Hey!
No... Aren't they on our side?
Perhaps he is under the belief that those taken hostage by the enemy
have betrayed Yamato.
But the Emperor wouldn't want this.
This is...
war.
Haku!
The Kamunagi of Chains, eh?
I will never forget
even the smallest things
The warmth you left with me
remains close to my heart
I will never be able to tell you
about the heartache I feel with you gone
I look up at the sky filled with shooting stars
and find you drawn in it
It feels as if I could reach you
if I just stretched out my hands
I used to be able to believe in hollow dreams
Where did my young heart go?
When did I become an adult?
So that was all?
I'd have been more impressed if they
were still willing to fight back, but...
Recall Oshutoru and Mikazuchi.
We have won this war.
I see.
So that's what happened.
I promise we'll take good care of the survivors.
Was there any need to go this far?
So many people died.
So this... is war?
Haku...
Let's go home.
Milady...
Episode 16
Banquet