Where... am I?
Am I...
saved?
What?
Umakeko...
Cover your eyes and ears!
A girl?
That was a close one.
Yeah.
Thanks for your help, um...
Kuon. My name is Kuon.
Kuon?
And you are?
Me? I'm...
Who... am I?
Episode 1
Curse
Does "Kujuuri" ring any bells?
Nope.
What about "Shishiri province"?
He doesn't seem familiar with the local geography.
He must be...
I've finished changing.
I'm coming in then.
Am I wearing this right?
I've never seen clothes like these before. They're kind of uncomfortable.
Well, I've never seen someone wear them that way, so I'd imagine so.
Huh?
R-Really? I thought something was off...
Isn't there an easier path we could take?
This is the easiest path.
Are you sure?
L-Let's take a break.
Again?
We just took one.
Cut me some slack.
My feet are killing me!
I guess he doesn't have much stamina.
Or maybe...
Did you say something?
No.
Anyway, if we're not out of here by sunset, we'll be food for the animals.
A-Are those things common around here?
What things?
Those slimy things.
Slimy things?
You know, like that nasty, gooey thing we saw in the cave.
You mean the curse?
Is that what they're called?
Yeah. If that's what you're talking about, then rest easy.
As long as you stay away from their territory, they're unlikely to attack.
Unlikely?
Well, there are always exceptions.
We'll worry about it if we run into one again.
A slight cold breeze is all it takes to kill a person, if the circumstances are bad.
Well, I suppose.
Don't worry.
I'm responsible for your life, since I found you.
Responsible?
I'll take care of you as your guardian.
My guardian?
And that's why I'm going to bring you to my village safely.
There, break time's over.
Hold on, let's rest a bit longer.
You can if you'd like, but the forest wakes up after sunset.
So if you're okay with being hunted, then sure, take your time.
If we keep up this pace, we should reach the village before nightfall.
Well, since I have no clue where I am,
following her is the best course of action right now.
I wouldn't survive out here for long by myself.
What are you doing!?
B-But...
You can't just touch a girl's tail without permission!
I-Is that thing real?
Of course it is!
No, but...
But there's no way people have tails...
And not just the tail; she has the ears too.
Apologize!
I'm waiting.
Ow...
And here I thought we'd make it.
I can't believe we're spending the night out here.
If you have something to say, tell it to the mountain and its stupid hills.
I've never seen someone voice their complaints to nature before.
Well, how is it?
What do you mean?
Have you remembered anything?
Nope, not a bit.
Wh-What is it?
You don't seem too concerned.
Well, it's not like I can do anything about it.
Maybe you're right.
Do you always travel around like this, Kuon?
Yeah.
So you have some kind of a goal?
I do have a goal, but it's not
anything particularly pressing.
More than anything,
I want to experience new sights and sounds in places I've never been before.
If I don't miss any opportunities now,
I can't regret them later.
You know?
Sound asleep already.
Finally!
Just a bit further, so hang in there.
H-Hey, where are you going?
To the inn.
The inn?
So Kuon's not the only one like that, huh.
You're a day late.
A lot happened.
Here are the herbs you ordered.
My, my, thank you.
Staying for the night, I presume?
Your usual room's open.
Two this time. Is that okay?
Two?
Hello.
Of course.
Just write your names here.
Thanks.
Um...
Is something the matter?
Come to think of it, what's your name?
I haven't got a clue, and I doubt it'll come to me if I try.
Not having a name is somewhat inconvenient, so let's think one up for you.
You're right.
Now that I think about it,
this might be a good opportunity.
With my missing memories,
I'm pretty much a blank slate.
I can come up with an awe-inspiring name without anyone objecting.
It needs to be one that I'll never regret.
In that case, I'll give you a name.
Sure, go ahead.
Wait, why!?
What do you mean why?
As your guardian, the responsibility of naming you rests with me.
Um, but...
If you think you'll be fine alone without my assistance,
then do as you please.
Fine!
Then it's settled.
Give me the most awe-inspiring name you've got.
Leave it to me!
Let's see...
If you can't decide, then I'll...
I've got it!
Haku!
Huh?
No, not "Huh." Your name is Haku.
Henceforth, refer to yourself as Haku.
Haku, huh.
It's plain.
Did you say something?
N-No.
This name comes from noble origins.
Noble origins?
Yes.
It's the name of one of Those Who Are Sung.
Haku, huh?
Come sit here, Haku.
Haku?
Hey, Haku!
It's not polite to ignore someone.
I'm still not used to being called Haku.
Cut me some slack.
But it's such a noble name.
So you say, but...
Did you say something?
Not at all.
You two must be close.
Here you go. Eat as much as you like.
Thank you!
What an absurd amount.
Without further ado, let's eat!
It's so good!
Don't tell me you don't know how to eat it.
Well, yeah, I guess.
Then allow me to demonstrate.
First, you take an amamu shell.
This thing?
Place meat, fish, vegetables, or anything you like on top.
Then wrap it around like so.
Ta-da! One amamunii, all done!
All done...
Dip in your choice of sauce and eat!
It's so good!
This is good.
Isn't it?
Dig in!
I would,
but there's nothing left.
That sure hit the spot.
Still eating?
If you're full, go ahead and use the bath.
Thanks, I think I'll do that.
Finally, a chance to rest.
I've been walking in the mountains for ages.
I'm stiff all over.
Ow...
The skin's all torn up.
I should probably stretch.
Let me see.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven...
Whoops, the towel came undone.
Oh well.
First, a shaking exercise to stretch my hands and feet.
Shake!
I can feel my muscles loosening up.
Next, let's up the speed!
Shake!
Now to add a spin!
What's wrong?
Nothing!
If you say so.
I'll make a salve for your wounds, so stay put.
Oh, thanks. That'd be great.
You're not really built for the mountains, huh?
Yeah, I found that out the hard way.
Sorry for pushing you past your limit.
Rest up for today.
Thanks, I will.
Hey, Kuon.
Thanks for everything.
Th-There, I said it.
Of course.
I'm your guardian, after all.
It's done.
It might sting a bit, but it'll do the job well.
How the hell is that "a bit"!?
It doesn't hurt at all.
Good morning, Haku!
Wash your face and get ready.
Get ready? For what?
We're going out to help the villagers.
Huh?
"He who does not work, neither shall he eat."
Once we get this stuff unloaded,
we can grab ourselves some grub!
Can't we rest a bit longer before working?
You'll heal quicker if you move around.
I'd just be in the way if I
suddenly barged in to help.
I've already spoken to the inn's owner.
I'm still worried about my feet.
Do they still hurt?
I'll bring the salve right away.
That's okay. No need for that.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
He's no good at cutting wood.
He's no good at drawing water.
Th-Thanks.
And he's no good at carrying goods either.
Hmm...
We used to grind amamu with the waterwheel here,
but it seems to be broken.
So we're using this instead.
And you want me to turn this thing?
That's right. It doesn't require
much strength, so you'll be fine.
See?
Well, if it's that simple...
Great!
Well, I have to attend to something. Do your best.
Well, I'll start with taking a break!
You'll start with what?
Do your job properly, please.
The village can't go without it.
Fine.
I guess I'll actually take this seriously.
How'd I do?
I gave it everything I had,
so it should almost be done.
That's all?
I quit!
I can't do this!
We're not supposed to do this manually, anyhow!
If it's broken, we should just fix it.
It doesn't look that complicated.
This is connected here,
that leads there,
and it transfers the energy from here and...
Aha! Here we go!
Is that lunch?
Yes.
Now that he's finally working, I thought I'd bring him lunch.
Ah, to be young.
He must be hungry.
All right! Now it's time to sleep.
My, how impressive.
Phew, it's not Kuon.
I heard the waterwheel was broken.
Did you fix it?
Yeah,
but don't tell anyone.
Why not?
If they find out, they'll give me more work to do.
Why should I get more work?
You're a funny guy!
Rest easy, I won't tell a soul.
I'm counting on you.
Yeah, see ya.
Okay, now I can...
Now you can what?
I said "He who does not work,
neither shall he eat," remember?
W-Wait, I can explain!
Don't, stop!
You should've just said that you fixed the waterwheel.
You started strangling me before I could even say anything.
Are you better at work that uses your head?
Why do I need to work so much in the first place?
Hm? Did you say something?
To a safe journey! Cheers!
Hey! It's a bit of a racket, I know,
but don't hold it against them.
Hey, you're...
I haven't introduced myself yet, have I?
Name's Ukon. I'm the boss of this bunch.
The Righteous Man
Episode 2