Wow! He's so cool!
It's a miracle we made it home alive.
Star wandering across the sky
glowing with ancient light
glimmer forevermore in the sky
and become my guide
The     False     Mask
Alone in the darkness
I blindly search
for something ethereal
but I believe I can find it
Alone in the endless night
I wander through the darkness
believing without doubt
that the sun will rise again
In times of despair
and anxiety
the only reason I was able to believe
was because you were there
Star wandering across the sky
glowing with ancient light
glimmer forevermore in the sky
and become my guide
I can no longer hold back
this feeling of love for you
It will reach you one day
and our hearts will become one
na
ri
te
become one
Episode 16
Banquet
Stop it...
Stop it, you idiot!
Akuruturuka...
Those granted the power of the masks.
Stop!
Haku?
May we come in?
Sure.
U-Um...
You're still in bed?
It's sunset.
It's my day off.
Yeah, but...
There's a place we'd like you to go to with us.
Please?
It's been a while since
we've all gone out like this.
Not since we first came to the capital.
Back when Haku-san didn't work and just lazed about all day.
Th-There was still a lot he
didn't know back then.
Right, Haku-sama?
Yeah! I couldn't believe
he didn't know how to read.
He was such a good-for-nothing back then.
That's the place.
It's so cute.
Yeah.
This would look perfect in your hair, Big Sister!
Catch you fancy?
Not really...
Listen, Haku...
You see, today, we wanted to...
What?
Nothing!
Anyway, how about you wait for us in front of the store?
Hey, come on...
Sorry for the wait.
You all done?
Yeah, just one more thing.
Here you go. It's from everyone.
Open it later.
H-Haku-sama, y-you can't do it
where other people are looking.
What are you thinking?
Th-That's perverted!
Yeah.
Look at it later, when you're alone.
Um, sure.
Haku... A lot's happened, hasn't it?
I was the first to find you...
Then we met all kinds of people.
Kuon...
What?
In that war...
I couldn't do anything.
Not a single thing.
Hey! How dare you worry my sister like that!?
Nekone!
And why do you look like
you're carrying the weight of the
whole world on your shoulders?
Who do you think you are, anyway!?
Everyone's got their own problems to deal with,
but they still have to do their best to survive!
Snap out of it already!
Haku!
Haku-sama!
Haku-sama! Haku-sama!
Well, look at that.
Kid sure looks like he's enjoying himself there.
What is this?
Okay, let's get started!
Yeah!
To Yamato's victory!
It's on me tonight!
Drink to your heart's content, everyone!
Okay, cheers!
Cheers!
We were just talking about having all
the guys get together for a drink.
No need to worry about the usual
subtleties without the girls around.
This isn't so bad every once in a while, is it?
I got us some good sake.
Sometimes drinking makes you feel better.
Haku-san!
Finally joining in?
Master Haku!
How dearly I've missed you!
Don't be so cold...
Here, have some more.
I simply yearn for love...
Oh? Now that I take a good look,
you're actually rather cute, Master Kiuru.
H-Huh!?
H-Hang on...
Your skin is so luscious...
St-Stop it!
I have Nekone-san already...
That is no issue! No issue at all!
I still require more love!
You sure are a lively bunch.
S-Stop that!
So you're Yakutowaruto?
Wh-What do you think you're touching!?
I hear you're good with a sword.
Stop... Stop it!
Hear you're not bad yourself, General Sakon.
Stop it, please!
Well...
How 'bout a little match?
What, you're drunk already?
What?
Afraid of losing?
How are you gonna be a strong father like that?
So noisy...
You're drinking a lot.
This is definitely quality sake.
That's right.
Hey, kiddo.
Whole bunch of idiots, eh?
You said it.
But they're worried about you,
even if it doesn't really show.
Listen, why don't you just get it
off your chest, whatever it is?
Well, I won't force you.
I do understand how you feel.
Do you really?
Do you really understand just how terrified I am now?
I do.
Like hell you do!
You're damn strong.
You're a damned veteran when it comes to war.
Haku...
I...
couldn't protect a thing.
Everyone's got to protect themselves.
Everyone on the battlefield knows that.
And I'm saying that I don't ever
want to go back to that battlefield!
That's not all.
War changes everyone.
They fight like it's the most
normal thing in the world.
And I can't stop it...
I can't take that!
I see.
You prefer their usual selves, don't you?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm happiest when I'm goofing
around with them every day.
I felt like I'd finally found
a place where I belonged.
But in that case, your only
choice is to hang in there.
Even if you close your eyes and run away,
no matter where you go, nobody will be there.
I've decided I'm going to protect
the Emperor and the capital.
Because they're the most
important things to me.
It's the same for you, right?
I know that.
You think I don't?
It's just...
I'm afraid.
M-Master Haku!
I...
I was so terrified there without you!
But I must work, or else I cannot pay off my family's debts.
Haku-san...
You were that concerned about us?
I'm so happy!
I'll...
I'll do my best too, even if I'm scared!
You heard it.
Doing your best for others
is important, isn't it?
I'm able to fight because I have Shinonon.
You guys...
Well, I'm invincible, so it's
got nothing to do with me.
What's so funny?
Nekone?
You guys getting closer?
Shut up!
You!
We're settling things right here and now!
Do I look good?
See?
Everyone's scared of war.
That's why we drink.
We party like fools.
I believe in you, and so do they.
Don't you think you can have a little faith in them, too?
Thanks, you guys.
But I kind of feel like
Ukon's trying to seduce me.
That's disgusting.
Having faith in your friends, huh?
Yeah.
We're strong, you know.
By the way...
If you're trying to make me feel better,
do a better job!
I've been watching, and I think
you guys just wanted to goof off.
And it's weird how you wanted to have
a party with just the guys all of a sudden!
You dummies!
To make you feel better?
Was that really the point?
Who can say?
You think the whole world
revolves around you, Master Haku.
Damn you guys...
I really was worried about you, Haku-san.
Probably.
"Probably"?
Okay!
Now that Haku's feeling better,
let the drinking resume!
Yeah!
All right, let's do it, Sacchan.
Right!
You guys get ready, too!
How is it, Nekone?
I can hear Haku-san,
and he sounds like he's having fun.
Thank goodness.
It sounds like Haku's feeling better.
Jeez, he's such a handful.
There really is no better cure than some time with the other men.
I guess I don't have a choice.
I'll lend him my brother for a little while.
By the way,
we're going to leave these two clueless
girls tied up a little while longer.
Got it.
Leave it to us!
Um...
I think they've probably run out of food by now.
Thanks, Rurutie.
Haku, everyone?
I'm coming in!
Master Haku, your body is marvelous!
You slackin' on me, kiddo!?
You need longer swings! Riskier maneuvers!
I see... Like this?
Indeed. When it comes to the naked dance, lightning speed is of the essence.
Master the technique!
I can see it! I can see it!
You ain't coverin' up a thing!
Kiuru-san.
It's time for you to strip, too.
I can't!
Wha— Stop it, Ougi-san!
H-Haku-sama...
Everyone...
Is this a dream? A fantasy?
Well, lookie here.
Guess the gents do the same things as us lasses.
N-No, Nekone-san!
N-Nekone?
Your eyes are scaring me.
Behold this gloriously toned specimen!
There is nothing to be embarrassed about—
Disgusting.
Nekone-san!
Look at all the wormies!
Shinonon, let's go somewhere else.
Okay!
Kiuru's is the cutest!
Live strong, Kiuru.
Cheer up.
I'm glad.
Looks like you've really cheered up.
Kuon...
Um, well...
I'm sorry.
Nah, it's okay—
What's wrong, Kuon?
Haku... Haku, you dummy!
Ow...
Ow, ow, ow...
The handwriting's too good.
It says they're worried about you.
It's like a love letter.
You shouldn't read over people's shoulders.
Sorry.
I didn't think Nekone would
send you one too, though.
Maybe I'll show it to Kiuru later.
Give the guy a break.
I'm grateful to them.
Yeah.
Can you really keep from changing, though?
You mean the power of the masks?
It may be more powerful
than most can handle.
But it's a sign of the Emperor's trust in me.
I believe in him.
War won't vanish from this world anytime soon.
But someday...
Well, there are some things in this world
that no amount of worrying will change.
And when that happens,
you do what we did today.
Drink and laugh it off.
That's certainly like you.
I used to fret over things, too.
But at some point,
I just stopped thinking about it.
Good, bad, all of that included.
I've become a pretty awful grown-up.
Yeah.
But I still don't like war...
I will never forget
even the smallest things
The warmth you left with me
remains close to my heart
I will never be able to tell you
about the heartache I feel with you gone
I look up at the sky filled with shooting stars
and find you drawn in it
It feels as if I could reach you
if I just stretched out my hands
I used to be able to believe in hollow dreams
Where did my young heart go?
When did I become an adult?
Episode 17
Afterglow