There you are, Your Highness.
What might be the matter, Woshisu?
Your Highness, a message has arrived from the forces in Tusukuru.
Three armies are insufficient?
Perhaps I underestimated Tusukuru.
I would ask you for a little more time, Your Highness.
General Raikou and the others will undoubtedly bring us victory.
How kind you are.
Surely you jest.
Woshisu, I shall wait a little longer for your sake.
Thank you, Your Highness.
However...
We must consider our next move, should it become necessary.
Star wandering across the sky
glowing with ancient light
glimmer forevermore in the sky
and become my guide
The     False     Mask
Alone in the darkness
I blindly search
for something ethereal
but I believe I can find it
Alone in the endless night
I wander through the darkness
believing without doubt
that the sun will rise again
In times of despair
and anxiety
the only reason I was able to believe
was because you were there
Star wandering across the sky
glowing with ancient light
glimmer forevermore in the sky
and become my guide
I can no longer hold back
this feeling of love for you
It will reach you one day
and our hearts will become one
na
ri
te
become one
Episode 20
Warrior
It seems I really cannot use it...
Do not engage the cavalry on their terms.
Hold formation and strike at them in groups!
We must break their formation.
Follow me.
Looks like it's true that they can't use them masks of theirs none.
Not to mention they're up against a scary opponent.
He's a class of his own,
both as a warrior and a commander.
This is an important stop on the route to Onkamiyamukai.
Of course Tusukuru would bring its greatest power to defend it.
I expected him to be here.
Let's go.
Have you any ideas for how to deal with Tusukuru's fortress, Master Haku?
Well, I mean, I need to think...
We do not have the luxury of time.
Why?
If he ever learns that we are struggling, he will act soon.
Vurai?
Tusukuru is strong.
Their soldiers and generals are beyond anything we've faced before.
They've investigated the masks and know how to deal with them.
But in the face of the man who was granted the
ultimate power by the Emperor, that means nothing.
Only soldiers should die on the battlefield.
I never want to see that again.
Let's end this war, and fast.
We got real close.
Pretty amazin' that you knew about this path, Kuon-han.
Nice work.
This place is my home.
So what do we do now?
You know...
Even the strongest soldier can't fight on an empty stomach, right?
You sayin'...
We target their provisions.
We sneak in while Munechika has the attention of their main force.
How do we sneak in?
Well...
I'm counting on you two.
Huh!?
You know, just make a path to take me to Old Man Mito.
Like you always do.
'Kay?
Can you not do it when everyone's watching?
Then you can stand a bit farther away...
Wait, can you only use that path yourselves or something?
That's a problem...
No.
A caster in that fortress has erected a barrier.
We cannot interfere from the outside.
Counter-magic is a fundamental part of defense.
Their general is too competent to forget that.
Really?
Yeah.
Then what?
What will you do?
What you gonna do?
Whatcha gonna do?
So that's it?
All right!
We'll break down the wall!
Yeah, not happening.
Then we'll dig a hole to the inside!
With just the four o' us?
Then we flood the place!
Where will we get the water?
Reckon we should just go back for the time bein'.
That's right.
Come on, Haku.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's go home for now.
Haku?
Why are you shifting your gaze?
I'm not.
You are, aren't you?
I said I'm not.
You came up with an idea, didn't you?
I-I don't have any ideas...
Really?
Really.
I see, I see!
You're not fooling anyone with that nonsense!
I feel like this hasn't happened in a while!
Spill the beans!
I haven't thought of anything!
Mister 'ere ain't usually this hardheaded.
I wonder what kind of idea he's got.
I'm going to squeeze it out of you no matter what!
My lips are sealed!
You're still not talking after all that?
I'll take it with me to the grave.
Weren't you the one who said you wanted to end this war quickly?
Fine, damn it!
Listen up, Tusukuru forces!
Open your gates immediately!
We have a hostage!
She's a citizen of Tusukuru,
and I can't guarantee her safety!
I'm the one who made him talk,
but I can't believe he came up with this.
You're a real scumbag, y'know.
See, this is why I didn't want to say it.
Bit late to say this now, but there's one problem with this method.
Which is?
It won't work if they don't believe Kuon's from Tusukuru.
You should have said that sooner!
If this falls through, we'll end up lookin' like pincushions!
That shouldn't be a problem.
Man, if looks could kill...
Some o' them are cryin'.
Forget that. Hurry.
That's right.
All right, now take us to the provisions storehouse!
That is, if you want this missy here back in one piece.
This way.
This is it.
Thanks, kid.
They're rollin' in food!
Are they eating better than we do in Yamato?
Just hurry up.
It's a waste, but I guess I don't have a choice.
Mister, heads up!
My lord, careful!
So very close...
I knew he'd be here...
My general said you were probably going to try something soon.
On the ball, he was.
Trying to set our food alight, were we?
I hope you didn't plan on leaving with your heads still attached.
He's a tough bugger!
Not bad.
What's the problem? That all you got?
Entertain me a little more!
Whoa there!
Atui! Yakutowaruto!
Worrying about others? Aren't you a brave one.
Crap!
Wait! He's...
He didn't hold back.
Whether you're a friend,
a parent, or a child...
If you're my enemy, I'll kill you!
Even you, the beloved child of the man I swore my soul to...
That is the law of the battlefield.
Kurou...
That's what it means to be on their side!
Am I wrong, young lady?
How are our losses?
Over ten percent.
Everyone is holding up well against the Rakusharai.
We must buy a little more time...
For Haku and the others who went deep behind enemy lines.
No matter how strong the enemy,
or how fierce the battle, we will not withdraw.
As soldiers of Munechika, that is who we are.
Indeed.
All troops, stand ready.
We shall repel the enemy!
That's strange.
I expected more from you, young lady.
See? Just like that...
Have you been slacking on your training since you left?
You shouldn't assume I love war the way you do.
Do you really intend to kill me?
You're begging for your life now?
I'm just asking.
Can you forgive me for betraying my country...
For betraying all of you?
Betraying?
Don't be stupid.
A little shrimp like you mixing in with the soldiers and fighting us
does no more harm than a bug's sting, from our perspective.
I'm right, aren't I?
If you were serious, you could tear this country in half.
If you're not doing that,
it means you're just here to play.
Do you know how much I
agonized over coming here?
And you say I'm playing?
Am I wrong?
Then...
K-Kurou?
What?
I-Is Sister Aruruu doing well?
Sure, I guess.
Does she still go on hunts for honey?
She does, but...
R-Right, right!
Speaking of Sister Aruruu...
Is Sister Kamyu doing well, too?
Where do you think you're going?
He caught me!
You got guts, kid.
I was so close...
I guess I don't have a choice anymore.
I'll set fire to it now!
The hell you will!
So you were holding back before, huh?
Who was it that taught me to hold her trump card until the very end?
I'm glad you remembered.
In that case...
So close.
He dodged that too?
Talk about killing my confidence.
Young lady, you...
If he's here, then I knew you would be too, Kurou.
It would be too dangerous to fight you head-on.
So I used trickery.
I'm ending this war, one way or another!
I see.
Interesting!
Okay, you two, now we get serious.
You can defeat him now!
Um, Kuon-han?
What?
I've been serious this whole time, y'know.
Same here. I was giving all I had.
Um...
You're not getting out of here alive.
Master Haku, is it time yet?
This seems like a good spot...
Okay.
Kuon?
You okay?
Yeah, but he is really strong.
Hey there, kid.
You ready?
Ready for what?
What else?
Ready to meet your maker!
You just don't know when to give up!
You got that right!
Stop screwing around!
I'm not gonna die here.
You ain't going anywhere!
Checkmate.
Now die!
You... That's...
Kuon, get out of here!
I won't let you escape!
That was...
He did it!
All forces, retreat.
Make haste to the fortress!
Strike them down!
All forces, follow me!
I'll kindly ask you to stay for a while longer
until our ally who attacked your fortress escapes.
He must be quite a man if he's worth all this.
He gives me the feeling that he's about to accomplish something.
I see.
I'll only say this once.
Stand aside.
Not while I still draw breath.
How regrettable...
I am Tusukuru's Samurai General, Benawi.
I am one of Yamato's Eight Pillar Generals, Munechika.
En garde!
I can't believe my memories of back then came in handy.
Okay, let's get out of here!
Yeah.
Man, that really hurt...
I thought I was a goner.
He survived that!?
Is he a monster?
Let's pick up where we left off, shall we?
Master...
We have come for you.
I'm saved!
Oh, no you don't!
Hey!
What?
Was it your idea to use the young lady as a hostage?
That's right.
What's your name, young man?
It's Haku.
Haku...
That name... That fan...
I see.
So that's him, young lady?
Even your strength exceeds mine.
But I will not be killed easily!
This sound...
It's the signal to withdraw!
I know... But...
This battle will be concluded another day.
Indeed it will.
All forces, retreat!
We're returning to base.
I will never forget
even the smallest things
The warmth you left with me
remains close to my heart
I will never be able to tell you
about the heartache I feel
I look up at the sky filled with shooting stars
and find you drawn in it
It feels as if I could reach you
if I just stretched out my hands
I used to be able to believe in hollow dreams
Where did my young heart go?
When did I become an adult?
What do you mean Raikou and the others withdrew?
Hey, Munechika?
We've received an urgent message from Yamato.
What happened?
The Emperor...
is dead.
My brother is... dead?
Episode 21
Death of
the Emperor